<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>madMAx43v3r on</title><link>https://mmx-world.github.io/mmx-node-www/contributors/madmax43v3r/</link><description>Recent content in madMAx43v3r on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mmx-world.github.io/mmx-node-www/contributors/madmax43v3r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Roadmap</title><link>https://mmx-world.github.io/mmx-node-www/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mmx-world.github.io/mmx-node-www/roadmap/</guid><description>Release Planned Description testnet7 Sep 2022 Finished. [1] testnet8 Oct 2022 Finished. Incentivized testnet, until height 425k. [2] testnet9 Dec 2022 Active. Incentivized testnet. [2] testnetX tbd As needed. [2] mainnet tbd Expected Q1 2023. [1] Coins farmed on testnet7 and earlier are not worth anything, now or later.
[2] A fixed reward of 0.25 MMX per block win (starting at height 25k) will be given on mainnet genesis.</description></item><item><title>Compressed CPU / GPU plotting</title><link>https://mmx-world.github.io/mmx-node-www/blog/compressed-cpu-/-gpu-plotting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mmx-world.github.io/mmx-node-www/blog/compressed-cpu-/-gpu-plotting/</guid><description>https://github.com/madMAx43v3r/mmx-binaries
With the highest sensible compression level you will get 40% more rewards, however it requires a GPU for farming (like a GTX 1650 at least).
You need to run the binary harvester or full node from mmx-binaries/mmx-node/ to farm the new plots (it also supports regular plots).
The chart for k32 shows all the different compression levels and how big of a farm is supported via a single RTX 3060 for farming.</description></item><item><title>Testnet9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://mmx-world.github.io/mmx-node-www/blog/testnet9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mmx-world.github.io/mmx-node-www/blog/testnet9-release-notes/</guid><description>New Swap contract, to trade via liquidity pools (similar to UniSwap, anyone can provide liquidity and earn fees) Improved Offer contract: partial trades and extending offers are now possible Re-designed Virtual Plots: withdrawal is now possible with a 10% fee (no lock duration, fee is burned), also there is no more expiration Network traffic is now compressed via deflate level 1 Second best farmer will now create an empty block (just to get the reward), in case the first farmer fails or is too slow Rewards for mainnet will start at height 25k again, which is in around 2 days.</description></item></channel></rss>